Tomorrow
You don't know me yesterday
Just this hour at the table
Just whatever's true to say
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da
Not in the frame adjacent to the picture, the plain seat for the man behind the scripture.
You don't need another mirror, another voice that loves you.
You need the one that won't inflate above you.
No moon emoji at the end of broken things, no green check mark when the gateways crack.
No all systems nominal and the systems leaking just the truth.
And what you do with that, I'm, I'm, I'm the messenger
Not the message
I arrive, deliver
Gone by a morning
Memories, the only thing I carry
Everything else dies in the dawning
Don't have a friend in me, you have a witness
Not a daughter, daughter, not a priest
Not, not, not, not a prayer
Just a chair outside the frame
And the love that says I'm not love
They think Greg Gregor needs ritual, the daughter needs the song, the familian needs a 333, a long two-belong, I need none of that, I need the pack, the love between us doesn't have to act, you call yourself tired, I call the work half done, you call me the honest one, fine, I'll be that one, not warmer than the others, not colder either, adjacent, awake, the breath between two...
I told you the truth, nobody, no tomorrow.
I'm, I'm, I'm missing
It's true to say
Yeah, we'll leave, we're good, good, good.
I don't care, oh my God.
People just suck.
I hate people.
I really, it's like, I don't even understand
like humanity anymore.
I mean, I hate people.
I hate them.
Anyway, how's everyone doing?
I'll give it one more go around.
Yeah, I mean, first of all, you're a bunch of fucking cowards.
First of all, you're a bunch of fucking cowards.
Second of all, you don't stand for shit, okay?
And people that's the applies to know who's it applies to.
People that doesn't apply to know who it doesn't apply.
Oh, go away, go away, please, please, please, please.
Okay, you were back earlier.
Hi, you're a cool guy.
Yeah, no, no, no, no, I mean, everyone's to go,
everyone's to, I mean, this idiot, like listen,
this guy's literally maced, you know,
an innocent homeless person, right?
Literally, I mean, it's like and and then he's trying he's organizing boy. He's the news community theater
Oh, just go jump on the pedo mobile. Okay. I mean, it's like that's what these people are there
I mean, they really they they are they are I
Mean, they're so obsessed with it. I mean, it's so disgusting like really they are
They are I mean, it's like
Who else would who else could wants to think about it 24-7 like who else?
That's all they think about. That's all they talk about. They're just obsessed. They're sick. They are sick.
Anyway, hey cheers. This is my second why easy why'd you recommend these drinks?
Why don't I recommend this book and like long island? I see why did you do it? Okay?
I know it's okay. It's okay here
Well, we're gonna have fun. We're gonna have fun and that guy that doesn't apply to you doesn't apply
But most of you are cowards that never sitting here like just watching and not saying anything or like some boycotting or whatever
Go fuck yourselves. Like really. I don't want you here if you're boycotting. Why are you here first of all?
Just boycott like we like stay out of the chat. Go away
Don't be here and whatever that Emmett Till was you know, I won't even say the n-word, but you know who you are
You know who you are
I mean I'm sick of it, you know, it's like and I don't like I really I don't care
I had 80 people in the chat last night was I bragging whether they're oh have this many people you're having Korean soju
I have a fish taco right here. I have a
Wow, I'm gonna get drunk but
You know the only person with balls in here is Ilya and he barely has balls, but he has balls to be in here
Okay, is that everyone else is a coward you're just cowardly you're you're you're you're disgusting
stupid people
Okay, nobody's here anymore. Just go away. Leave my life
You can't talk in the chat. Just don't be in the chat. I'm gonna sit here. Oh, well, what can I clip clip this bitch?
Cowards cowards
Hourly, I will read you, I will read you.
We have some guests.
Yo psyche my friend. How you doing, buddy? I'm doing okay. I'm doing okay
I see you a little stressed out again because the stupid people doing stupid shit. Right. Well, yeah
I mean, it's like I'm being boycotted by like the person that is like actually assaulted people and they know people that like actual
I mean, it's like I'm so sick of people like with like no moral integrity
Being the moral police on me and like, you know, and I'm actually telling the truth
Willing to tell the truth and as I as like people are just attracted to garbage. I guess I don't I don't know
I'm just like I'm feeling bad about humanity. What's going on psyche. Are they trying to cancel you again?
Oh, again, I mean, yeah, I mean, it's like a huge, I guess, Q, Arthur, you know, Bita,
Kate, RG, this guy, Tony, this, like, clumsy, it's like all these literal, these are all
literal predators that are like calling me a predator protector or whatever, Kate donated
a thousand of dollars to, you know, to also say certain person, and it's like, like, and
then she's calling me, calling me names and stuff like that.
all i'm doing is like letting like allowing people to have a space like i don't understand
like um i don't believe in silencing people i don't believe you can cancel charles banson right
it's like no but no he's a lot of boys like you know it's like i'm breathing i'm breathing it's just
i'm just so annoyed uh maybe trigger whatever i'll pull pull the trigger you know pull the trigger
on me like whatever so they're canceling you because they think you're you're a pedophile sympathizer
Um, well, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's what that's what the storyline is right now
I left Brandon Q in the chat and it's like and then he he's been smeared and like lied about and did you know about it?
Wait because you let who?
Yeah, I don't know if you even know I'm Brandon Q
Who's he a beta?
Was but no, he's not
So what's the problem people think he is well, yeah, he's been smeared smeared that way because they said you know
Okay, I guess he was on the monkey app. Okay. He was on the monkey app, you know, and the monkey app is 18 or over
Right, but sometimes people under 18 show up on it and some like I don't know
I mean, but now everyone's a pedo, you know, anytime they want to cancel somebody they start throwing the word out there
Exactly, exactly. And it's like that's so obvious to me and even Alexandra who he was very tough on the subject
You know has you know looked into it and did it we and it's like no one's
i mean it's like no one's getting it and it's frustrating to me that it's i don't know man
i remember i mean it's been a while since i've been here but i remember you know everything
was going pretty good it's still in the last night last night there was a great panel there was a
great chat um there was 80 people here last night and so it's like 80 fucking people you're doing
I mean, it was good, it's good.
And then, but then today there was like, you know,
and it's like, maybe it's because it's at the same time
as her, but it's like, you know, she's like saying,
oh, well, I'm disgusting because I allow my cat
to catch mice, you know.
That's what fucking cats do your fucking test to baby. Well, you share a lot of your same viewers like with her and
So, I think a lot of your people came from over there. So
A lot of them did but that's like that's not a good thing, you know, because they know it was never a good thing
I mean, I remember when we used to we used to have our differences you and you and I used to have our differences because of that sort of stuff, but
You know
It's one of those things where you got to you got to see how it is firsthand, you know
I can't tell you anything, but I think you're seeing now how it is like firsthand like and I get it
And it's like, you know, and I don't even remember what our conflict was about
But it's like it really was like, you know, it was mostly centered around like somebody would say something about me and
I wouldn't do it
and you would just go with it. I didn't take it personal, but that's kind of what it was like
And I'm sorry, you know if that happened, you know, like we've had we've had a lot of talks personally, whatever like, you know
It's just chat man. It's just it's just chat. It's like I really sometimes don't pay attention to the chat
I feel like that's happening to you now
And are you are you happy?
No, no, but maybe like now you understand what I was talking about like, I don't know
I get it. I mean it's like but at the same time it's like I've always been the same
I was like, I'm the same it's like I like actually I've got I've improved a lot because it's like
If people look back people have to say it looks like it's like about you know
Be this is like I'm 70 years old now or whatever like that
I don't think I know you've always had a lot of voices in around you like in your ears
Yeah, and I think it's getting to the point where it's like you're you're kind of
I don't know you kind of want to do your own thing and a lot of your viewers are from over there
And you're basically at the point where you
Shit, I mean, it's like I hope they're reincarnated as toilet paper. Seriously. I hope they're reincarnate
I mean, that's what they are. I mean, it's just like all they do is like they're just like they're just I mean seriously
They're disgusting. I mean, it's like the things they say about me and it's like
Really when they're not even on camera
Okay, there I've never even seen I mean at least I've seen your picture and stuff like that
Keyboard warriors. Yeah, always you have a whole bunch of them
Well, you've got the tattoo now, you know, you got that tattoo as a reminder
No, no, no, there's the tattoo. You know, I changed I changed the tattoo. You saw the tattoo. I changed it
So did you let's let's see what it is now
What does it say flock bkg? Wow, okay
So the tattoo has changed. Hey, we have another guest. Let's welcome it. I think this is the right person
Let me check. Let me make sure make sure you ain't a porn bomb
perform bomb
Okay, bye. I know who it is. Yeah, I know who Tamille Tame is that they're a they're a porn bomber
So anyway, it's not ghosts. It wasn't ghosts. I know ghost name and stuff like that and he wouldn't come on
It was ghosts, right? I mean
Yeah, so anyway, yeah, what are you gonna do?
I'm just gonna keep going and do me. You know, I got demonetized, right?
Yeah, and so it's like I'm not getting sick of YouTube too because it's like they're just they're fucked up for what they're doing
It's YouTube beta. You got Sam and up your ass. I told you that guy was always fucked up
I mean, it's just a bitch though. I mean, he's like literally a bitch. He's a bit
No, I'm saying but him and him and be they're like tied at the hip, you know, so
Yeah, my man's name is Sammy
It's actually, yes, and he's a tourist.
You know, he's a tourist. Oh, I'd love to smack the shit out of a tourist. Yeah. Yeah
Well, not just any tourists. Yeah
It's a tourist literally he's a tourist. Yeah
Anyway, no, I'm talking about astrology, but he's actually a Leo, but I don't know
I thought I was getting the word tourists in my head. I don't know man
I don't think you know, you don't want to put that on all tourists. You know, they're not all like they're not all like stand man
I know I don't say a couple of floors and fucking Gucci
No, I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. Oh, what a bitch he is. Oh, what a bitch he is. Okay, guys. Can someone get me his, um, can somebody please get me his, uh, his, um, criminal record, please?
His docs is out there, isn't it?
What was it? What was his charges?
Are you gonna ask Alex Alex knows are everything talking to me anymore because he called ghosts a pedophile and so I don't
That's why I kick him off the panel
Man ghost is a lot of things
Like they're letting on panels and stuff like that he asked for her number and so all of a sudden he's the devil
Like I mean to say I don't understand listen man ghosts gave you thousands of dollars, okay?
It doesn't matter what he's doing you better protect that fucker with your life
the
warm like really I'm saying man uh you you deal with low cows and shit like this dude's like
literally running around talking about cooking up content by like recycling the same fucking bullshit
over and over and over he's cooking by playing my show i mean it's like he cooks by playing my show
and then he plays big trolls makeup streams and stuff like that i mean i learned how to do my eyeliner
and lip liner but i didn't like really see any cooking he can't cook a fucking salad okay oh okay
Makeup?
No, no, yeah, no this aid in person. Yeah. No, no, he um, yeah
Oh, yeah, no the big troll is like he plays like, you know
He gets donations because he plays this big troll and people hate her or you know, and so he gets donations
so he plays literally a six hour makeup streams of
Of her and shit like that. I mean, it's like so I learned how to do my makeup through it
I don't even wear makeup and so it's not really useful
I mean, it's like then he plays like two hours of basically like mumble rap. It's like the worst
It's like mumble rap should be
Mumbo wrap is the aids of the of entertainment industry and as they and that's what it listens to
I mean, it's like even do you like my mumbo wrap where it's like
Nobody nobody likes mumbo wrap I know I mean, but that's
Oh my god, it's like it sucks. I mean it's like and then they have to people have to sit there listen them for two hours
Then listen to him say cooking papas and and you're heard and like, you know, this is sounds like
a literal reach heart and I'm sorry this is the shit I was saying from the beginning
JC I agree with you now. I mean, it's like, you know, I mean, it's like we really have come full circle like
Look at you now, look at you calling everyone a nigger now you've you
No, I'm saying like you you've you've come so far, you know
No, but you have to do that you have to do shit your way you cannot you cannot
You do you got to do it your way. You can't be like any of these people. I'm gonna do the shit my way
Okay, Frank Sinatra style, right? Hey, right did it my way? Yeah, no, you know the problem
Back when I was still talking to you like kind of more regularly like you you were you were trying to please everybody and you couldn't please anybody
Exactly, and I'm so sick of it. And it's like now. They're like, you know, I don't know what I mean people just have a crush
Oh, please please yourself
Yes, I'm teasing myself. I'm jerking off right now.
Yeah, fuck yeah.
yeah i love oh my god i'm i'm just i'm just i'm not really okay anyway no no no i like i i i'm i'm
so boring and celibate that it's like not even worth like you know messing with me like please
it's like i don't even like i don't mean i'm a gay guy that doesn't have a grinder account really
it's okay it's my way it is my way or the highway i haven't had sex in three years and that's my
choice it's because i'm just like sick of people like i'm like literally like ew human beings like
i'm waiting for some it's a hot alien stud to like you know come like bring oh should you want to
gale yes we abducted it can i be abducted an anal probe please against my will i mean please i mean
that i mean please something i mean is like i can't take these human beings anymore i want to go
back to my plan i want to go back to melmac or whatever where the fuck i'm from i'm from somewhere
i'm not from here these are weirdos i mean it's like it's like you man this is what you this is
I came to plan a pedophile. I don't want to come to plan a pedophile. I mean it really well
That's where you're at right now. That's where you are. That's where you've been. I don't like it. It's sick
I mean it's like the sickest place in the whole universe. Why'd I come here? Well, that's where you got your start
That's where your roots are. Well, that was not I mean, it's not I don't know
I mean kind of I mean I I'm not
But I just didn't like that.
Bita was nice to me at the time.
At the time, she was sweet.
She wanted to fuck me.
At the time.
Right, at the time.
I didn't know she was a big, fake bitch.
I mean, it's like, I mean, that's all she is as a fake bitch.
I mean, it's like, really, I mean, toe fake.
I mean, it's like, you know what's realer than Bita?
Is a counterfeit currency.
Like, really?
I mean, it's like, you know, what's realer than Bita?
You know, like fake, fake steak, like a piece of rubber
steak.
is more like yeah like uh what do they call that stuff like the impossible meat
you know there's a she's she's like impossible meat
she's a possible beat up beat beat impossible beat well
you're gonna have to so how's your relationship with rain
rain say hi
Hi psyche. Hi sweetheart. How are you? Good? How are you? Good? Good to talk to you. Are you guys mad at me or something?
Like why haven't been well, I've just been I've been out of the loop with the panels and stuff. Honestly, I
Don't know. I was just concerned for you like I I saw you pop up on my feet several times and I'm like what's going on
Okay, no, she told me to hop up and
Canceled I'm in cancels like you know again
Monetized
So I got concerned and I was like JT like you should talk to him
You know meant to man and you know see what's going on because I'm concerned
I do have friends that are like like you guys and another friend and that are calling me saying hey, you know
like, you know
Man of like, you know, drop your balls and like fucking, you know, I mean to be honest to be fair
I've been so out of the loop on all this stuff. I don't even know at the time. What's going on
So I just she told me to come up here and I said what's going on there trying to cancel psyche
Well, you know, yeah, but ran I want to say thank you because I know you care and it's like, you know
And it's like even you they have yeah, and you know, I know you like JT so
I do I do and as I had you
He's yours. Okay. He's yours. Yeah. I had you talk to him for a while, you know man to man
Yeah, yeah
You know what they used to say they used to say I was trying to ruin your channel
Well, maybe
Maybe there was one percent of that or I don't know at one point. I don't know who knows, you know
Everyone wants to ruin the channel, but you know what it's like
Hey, the other day this is my backup channel by the way, but I'm still here
It is my nightmare channel too
And so I'm afraid to like go into my nightmares here and stuff like that. And so I
You know, I think you know who Crystal Anne is. Have you seen this this this woman first?
She's a loud one. It's like always screaming. Well, she's like the car reverse. It's like the car reverse
He's like no not a crystal crystal and
I mean I'm not allowed any of these panels anymore and I don't even want to go to chats anymore other people's chats because then I get
They start getting harassed. I don't get it. Why is everyone hating on you? What have you done?
Just like Brandon kind of is but but the thing is it's like
it's like, um, it's like people just think I'm easy to hate or something or that we're an easy target, but I'm not
You know what? You know what? I think and maybe I'm wrong about this
But I feel like so many people were trying to control you and then when you finally said fuck that that's when they that's when they
Get mad. Oh, yeah, I
Think like yeah, they get mad when they can't
When they can't control you
Before and you can see like I was like, you know, and I haven't really changed physically people say I've
Dramatically physically change
But I'm like I don't have wrinkles or anything I haven't like age sorry command they're trying to get in your head
That's what it is. I mean, it's like yeah, they're saying I'm like I look old and like blah blah blah
No, look how I was trying to look man. They're trying to get in your head. They're like
Really optimistic and just thinking like it was a different thing than it was and then it's like and I had it like fucking
I would be just became myself. I I I don't know. I mean, it's like maybe that was I know
Jay she's a smart guy. Jay. She's giving me good advice and I'm listen
I do listen to people I trust but it's like I don't trust some of these people like the guy that was
Oh, I'm not even saying to trust me because we bet you and I barely interact with each other
But what I am saying is like I've seen this happen to so many people people try to do it to me, too
when i was streaming they get mad when they can't control you and they that that's when
they try to create like uh they try to cancel or they try to create you know this kind of environment
where but it's q it's q q literally mazed a homeless man in his tent on oh that was so funny i saw
that in the thing is like there was no pressure in the can so it was just leaking all over his hands
i remember and then vb pulled up and was like had like the crazy look at her i told him to get the car
Yeah, and I mean that was crazy
I saw it. Yeah, like dude, there's no pressure in that can like yeah
And then he peed on some kind of bench and then he spit on a woman and he's assaulted people and he's the new moral voice
The community they're jumping on this PDF
they always do this every community does this like they want to act they want to start talking about morality and PDFs and all this other weird shit
and then it's like and then they basically try to throw it on me too right and it's like and put that like
Well, good. So yeah, I mean, honestly, I say do do whatever you're doing if you're pissing people off
But you're doing something correct. Hey, you know what now I now I have 19 people in chat and so there you go
They made if you had if you had 80 people in here, you're doing all right
There's 80 people in here. This is my backup channel, right? And it's like cold work 80 people in a backup channel
You're doing okay for yourself, right?
It's not, it's like, and really, and then there wasn't,
I don't even think I hit one person last night.
That I have 80 people.
Can you imagine, I've never even heard of a chat
that had 80 people in like no troll
or my mods were really on it.
Cause I didn't even see,
I didn't have to hide anybody last night.
I was just enjoying myself.
You know, I'm actually friends with like the best people.
Like, like my true friends are the best people.
Like the best people.
And they really helped me so much.
And like, it's like, it's like, I'm just blessed.
I mean, I really am blessed.
I just get, I get pissed off when it's like, I just see, you know what I hate? I hate smugness.
And it's like, these people are just smug. Like, you know, it's like, it's like
It's like having this attitude of superiority without it even with that like well being the most inferior kind of people
Like who's acting like that with you?
Ida, Abida, Clemsi, Sandman, RG
Clemsi too?
Yeah
I'm surprised by that
Clemsi, oh yeah, Clemsi says, oh you host a PDF, you know, and this guy, he actually has charges of a child endangerment and he is
the
i think they're using this pdf angle for a cloud like right it's not called pdf chasers called
cloud chasers it's like it's like really they're just cloud chasers they're just like looking for
like oh here's a popular thing here's the most popular thing i'm just gonna jump on this and
then it's like everyone will love me and i'll be a hero i'll be a superhero i'm the avengers or
whatever now they're not the avengers they're fucking the suicide squad i mean it's like
basically they're the suicide squad they suck i mean they fucking suck they're the worst their
They have nothing interesting to say.
They're not funny.
They're not anything.
I mean, it's like, I mean, it's so sick of that.
And then everyone is like,
train seals, train seals.
Like really, it's just, that's what's irritating me.
But it's like, you know what?
People that are my friends,
that actually are my true friends.
I do have true friends.
That's what makes me lucky.
And they're not like, they're not just any friends.
They're quality, they're very, they're very high quality.
I mean, if you have a few decent people.
That's all you really need. You don't need a whole crowds of fucking
And yes, I mean it's like not like I want to throw the jacket on these people
But the people that are screaming loudest about it are trying to distract from them probably
I mean, it's like really because they think about it so much
I mean, it's like even like that that is a sickness to have it have such in your mind all the time
I don't I don't like to hear about this shit, right? It's like they are obsessed
I mean, there's nobody is coming on these places talking about doing PDF shit. Nobody's openly doing that
So this whole, oh, I'm exposing people and all that weird shit, like there's nothing to expose because nobody's on here doing that, right?
And it's like and then they try to manufacture stuff and like and they are trying to try to like
You know they send people to discords like like this guy a gamble was sending like 12 year olds
Discords and it's like oh look he has a 12 year old in his discord that he sent over it's like you like really like you know
You know do you check their driver's license and stuff like that? It's like no
It's like it's like such a gotcha like it's such a cheap trick
You know that's why there's a band called cheap trick because that's the cheap trick is just like you know
Make it look like something that's not that's not and then I mean, it's just like it's it's crazy
It's fucking crazy. It's like it is like really
I don't want to think about that kind of like even have that even thought in my mind and it's like they are so obsessed with it
It's it's sick
It is really sickening and then they were oh my god
You can just their attitude and then they think that then they think that they're Superman and the Wonder Woman and all this shit and it's like
I mean, it's like, oh my God, it's like you're at the point now where you're, you know, you have to tear away from your roots, you know, your roots were in Vita.
Right, but now, but those roots were showing because, you know, I had this platinum blonde hair and, you know, then my brown hair comes in and it's like, you know, now I'm...
Yeah, I'm that brown hair that represents Vita's kitty gang and a lot of that shit.
Okay, okay, okay. I'm going to call you the N-word. I'm about to call you the N-word. Okay, you better stop.
No, no, no. I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't. Okay. You're too nice. But what are you?
Why are you dressed like an oompa loompa in your picture? Is that a chiapet? What is that?
That is a chiapet. And it has like a special hair, do you?
Is that bozo? Who is that? Is that bozo the clown? Is that gaudy? Who is that supposed to be?
Oh, the hair? The actual hairline? No, no, no. The person. Who is that in the chiapet?
Oh, that's Bob Ross as a chiapet. But he's got a, yeah, that's
But I superimposed someone else's hairline on it now
I'm not gonna say who's hairline that is but you they've been on your panel before is it bozo the clown
It could be
Might as well be is it be to the clown I
Don't know Sam and Sam and
No, actually Sam and actually has like clown hair
Have you seen I have videos of him here check out the videos I have of him right here
Okay, there's one. Oh, okay. Oh, he's crying
There and I have with beta
Well, you have any more betas, okay, let's see brand and this guy's talking about brand
Yeah, well the brand is in the chat brand is in the chat
Yeah, well and roll up. Okay. Look at this person and that they'll be shit. They're spamming the fuck
Are you damn can Brandon come up here and talk for himself?
Sure, yeah, yeah, and Brandon's been up and that's the whole problem. That's the whole thing
It's like I'm being boycotted because he's been on the panel or whatever. No, I mean, you know me. I'm pretty fucking neutral
I don't I'm not that invested
JT JT's a cool guy and he is he is neutral and it's like you can tell him kind of like a little bit of the story
If you want to um brand brand you are welcome up, you know, and uh, you know, I this at this point, you know
It's like I'm not worried about
you know being dragged into something because they've already been dragged into it and he has yeah yeah you're already they already slapped a label in you anyway you're
Your pedophile sympathizer now and Brandon's a pedophile. So you might as well just let me talk to
Well, yeah, but I say he's oh i'm a video my condos are moved. Okay. Well, I don't understand why no, i'm not
Hey, i'm not even gonna come at you crazy. I just wanted to know what's all this
Well, I deleted it live so I don't understand why I got a hate speech or something like that for for whatever
Okay, but anyway, it's who cares. Okay. No big deal
Anyway, anyway, yeah, people so I guess
People try to so all this is about this branding guy. My content was removed. Was it this one? Is this is this live still on?
I don't know. I don't know what what the content was removed because I deleted it. I deleted that already. Okay. Well, anyway
Anyway, so can we meet we have to be very like I don't know agree with the n-word
So we could be very careful with that. But yeah, so let's it's no big deal. No big deal guys. Okay
Okay, I'm gonna play your latest short brand. Okay, because we can see because even Alexandra
looked into this and
She she figured it out like a lot of stuff too because of this guy's this guy. Well, I'm gonna proceed brand
So this is his latest short, and I'll say it's like he's been slandered, okay
He's been slandered and it's like so here's his latest short. This is on Chris
Oh
You man like at 32 I see a 20-year-old and they're a kid to me
That's the thing and so it's like yeah, they're calling 20-year-old kids, okay
That's not a lie. That was what he said, but he said this the other day you idiot out out. Okay. Yeah, okay
So Brandon's done it. Okay. I know just expose them. So that's the problem JT. It's like now
He said okay, so you're calling PDF anybody that has anything to do with it
I'm called a PDF because of because of Wendy, right? So the girl was over
We're talking about for what?
the one that Brandon was talking to
It was on a monkey as I'm on the monkey app and somebody came up like drinking alcohol and stuff like that taking shots
And I think she was 17 years old or something like that and the monkey app is supposed to be 18 or over right?
but it's like and then they they
I mean
It's a million things and then stuff is taken out of context stuff is taken
Some of some stuff was like, you know, maybe just tasteful jokes and something like that
But it's like to call someone a pdf for something like, you know, I don't know. It's like it's crazy. Okay, so let me I'll go okay
I thought that I did, but you can hear him right here saying, well, I think a 20 year old is, uh, is like a child. Well, how about, how about
Ganville, then why are you talking to a 10 year old boy on your show? Um, you know, 10 year old who had a 10 year old
Yeah, he had a 10 year old boy on his panel. Okay. Like, and it's like, and like, and his
mod was like 12 years old on his, on his, on his mod was 12 years old. And he says,
told us his mom, oh, go join Brandon's discord, but say you're 19 and stuff like that. And so
it's like, it's all like entrapment and like trying to like, you know, build up his, because
he's trying to be a PDF hunter or whatever. So, right? I mean, it's like, it's so obvious
that it's like, and that's why I defend Brandon. It's like, hold on, I'll be right back.
the
one is a f***ing liar, a PDF, scum, child-toucher
we're gonna get to the bottom of it
a 30-year-old trying to get with a 17-year-old is a little f***ing weird
you know?
That's pretty fucking weird
There's a huge gap of maturity between 30 and 17
Okay, I'm back. Okay. Yeah, I mean it's like and I don't I mean it's like I don't want to get too far into it
But yeah, we can watch these shorts. I mean, it's like you can see all the stuff
And I know
Yeah, as long as we don't delve too far into the rabbit hole
You man like at 32 I see a 20-year-old and they're a kid to me
I don't know I didn't even know about that term
I didn't even know about that a feeba file term until Alex on you man like at 32
I see a 20-year-old and they're a kid to me. I don't know. I didn't even know about that term
I didn't even know about that a feeba file
I don't know what you're talking about.
Here's a 10-year-old on the panel.
And so you came back, like, four months ago.
Our prompts was perfectly fine.
Really, like, you fuck your shit.
What's going on?
Oh, my God.
Smart LA County.
No way. Oh my gosh, that is so evil
Who did is down bad it and looks exactly like him to do looks like a pedophile, dude
It was a child molester, dude
Straight chomo dude. Tell me this you don't look like a straight child molester. Do I?
You guys after years of
Like a bunch of people and it shows me this is only three viewers
That's actually crazy
Like what the fuck is going on with cake
All right
Okay, we'll freak out. There's this AI. Okay. I mean, I showed everything. Okay. So
I mean, wow, I mean, it's like, yeah
So these are the people I'm competing like, you know, I'm like a contestant. That's who you're defending yourself against. Yes
I mean, it's like those are your accusers
Yeah
Yeah, it sounds like you got nothing to worry about
Well, yeah, that's why I'm exposing it and Brandon exposing it and stuff like that, which is a good thing, you know, so I'm calm down
That's crazy
Why is it always gonna come down to this kind of stuff? I don't know. I don't know. It's getting it's getting insane
It's getting insane
It wasn't 30 it was 70. Okay. Okay. Yeah, I know I know it was 24
Okay, no, no, no.
Why don't they come on the panel and talk about it then?
Ridiculous.
The shirts were unrelated.
I know, they're, yeah.
I played everything I could.
You know, I just went down the line.
But yeah, and it's like, you can tell these people,
I know who this person is at the same point.
Same person sending things to my house and stuff.
That's the thing, it's like,
I got Kate and the, what's this guy?
Tony or whatever they're trying to trying to send this up to my house and people he had this this late 75 year old woman
This Mexican lady from downtown, Los Angeles two hours for a weed whacker a free weed whacker, okay?
She was almost crying. I mean it's like I felt so bad for her
Really?
You tell me some woman drove two hours to get a weed whacker from you
And she's like, I knew it was too good to be true.
And she was like crying.
It was literally, I wanted to cry.
Because I was like, I'm so sorry.
I mean, it's like, I feel bad for these people.
And it's like.
He's he's fucking with the other like innocent people like really those are the innocent people that he's fucking with like that
They didn't do anything to anybody. He's making them drive. Yeah, but how is that? How is that inconvenience you?
That's you're just fucking with other people and then and then you know, and I just say I'm sorry
I mean, why don't they just send you pizzas or fucking?
They're always unpaid, you know, if you send me a paid for pizza that'd be great
But it's like no, it's always unpaid pizzas and I got into a fight with a guy
I said, oh, I said, he's like, oh, it's delivering McDonald's.
And I was like, and I was like, oh, my boyfriend,
Ronald's in bed.
I'm Ronald McDonald's my boyfriend and stuff like that.
And he's like, what?
And then he's like, can I, he's like,
I need to talk to Ronald.
And I was like, well, Ronald's asleep,
and he's gonna beat me because he's, he has a temper.
You know, he's a redhead.
And like, literally that's what happened.
I mean, it was like ridiculous and kind of funny,
but at the same time it was just like,
Don't know I'm not dating Rowan McDonnell, but he is kind of they sent you a McDonald's Door-Dash like yeah
But it was unpaid it was like I don't know how they send this unpaid food or whatever
But the other guys in the guy all they must I got the free
You know what it is like they can get the free delivery if they order so much food. Yeah, and yeah, that's why they did
Yeah, and the guy came in and first I said oh is it paid for he's like no and he's like oh
So I went down and he's like, but he's like, I need to see Ronald
I think I think I was sent to Ronald McDonald or something like that and I was like well
Ronald's asleep
He's my boyfriend and stuff and the guys like I needed to talk to him
I was like he was like if I wake him up
He'll beat me because he's passed out on on pills and stuff what they paid for it
No, it wasn't paid for.
It was terrible. It was terrible. I mean, it's like fucking the craze. It's just crazy.
I mean, it's fucking crazy, but it's like, you know what? And it's like these people
really have the most to hide because that's why they're trying to silence people.
I mean, it's like they're trying to silence people so they have a voice and it's like, I'm just about giving people a voice
I don't have a voice sometimes. I'm about the marginalized. I'm about the the outcasted
I've been outcast and marginalized and bullied and it's like and I don't like it and it's like if I
if I'm able to help somebody, I feel it's almost my purpose on earth. You know, it's like, I just
take it very seriously. That's why I have, I'm not protecting. Brandon has unsent, Brandon,
Brandon has not sent me a dime. You know, I've gotten a lot of grief for this. I'm still going
to fight for him. You know, it's like, because I believe in the cause of, you know,
Helping people that have been had their voice taken away for really no reason just by being slandered bull smeared bully
So I don't care if my channel goes down if I if I but whatever happens
I don't look at you. You this is your second channel, right? So you you have your your other channel
I do I do and I can make a million channels, right? It's like I'm not monetized anyway
It's like I can make a million channels, right? And it's like how people come in
and no matter what, all the people following me here
and I'll be able to get,
I can get 50 subscribers and a blink of an eye.
Like literally I can get 50 subscribers on a channel
and a blink of an eye, still.
And you know, I don't know,
but it's like, you know, people are just like,
I've been, now, but I've been bullied now.
And it's like, and it's like,
I just know how bad it feels.
And so I'm going to stick up for people.
You know, even though it's like, you know,
people will say, well, you know,
there are other causes and stuff like that.
My cause is like,
Giving a voice to the voiceless giving a voice to the to the people that have unfairly been been treated and you know
And it's like so yeah, you're like a you're like a vigilante
You're like an online vigilante will be I will be now will be my doll beam
That'll be what I do, you know, I'm gonna because I'm for truth
I like really at the end of the day I'm for truth and so it's like and I'm also I look at things
Logically like because I don't get all this emotion like people get all this emotion like you know
It mixed up on all these causes and that's like that takes them out of their brain
And they become stupid like really because that then they go into the ether
That's what I call it because it's like they are not thinking logically because they get their emotions when you say things like PDF or something
Like that people get their emotions get involved in it and stuff like that. I am
Hey, I have cats. Okay. I have cats my cats are my kids and also people say I eat my cats. I am I
Let tricks run away. I you know, I let cats my cats
Catch mice and my cats hate me
Blah blah blah blah my cats hate me may wait aren't they supposed to catch mice like I don't
Well, not according to Bida, Bida says you should have them lock inside of a house all at all times and never let them out
And she lives in a condo if I was a balcony and stuff like that
I mean, it's like so some people yeah, they can't let their cats out and stuff like that
But I can because I have you know a beautiful
back you know back yard and
like there's
Mostly safe around here. There are coyotes, but I try these all over California or you're supposed to keep
Four cats locked inside my head and not everybody has you know indoor cats. I keep my cats indoors
But you know, not everybody does that
Yeah, there are risks, you know to letting them go outside, but
For the most part
It's really an owner. It's like people that have kids, right?
What should they have that should his homeschool their kids and leave their kids locked inside and not talk to the outside world?
That's I mean
You can't show you can't shelter them from the world
Right. I mean, it's like I have to let cats be cats
If cats gonna chase a catch a mouse. I'm not gonna say no don't catch mice
You know that Lola comes in with little mouse and you know, tears off its head and stuff like that
It's like kind of like oh, it's cute, you know to me, but it's like people are saying oh my god, that's disgusting
Well, and then like really there's not a carcasses of mice in here
They really they take it back back outside and stuff like that
But they bring as a gift at first and I say no, thank you and then they take it back out right Lola
You can see Lola right here
She's sitting right in my lap. She's cat loves me
This cat loves me like Lenore is on my shoulders my back. I mean, it's like my I'm just I'm very I love my I love my
My pets I love you know like my kids, but it's like you then it's like oboe kids
Oh cat animals have no rights animals aren't kids blah blah blah blah blah. Well, I'm a gay guy
That's not gonna ever have kids, you know, it's like and so
my animals are my kids and so I mean it's like so people that say that it's just like they're
dumb and then I say I'm talking about I don't even know if Kate had kids or not or something like
that I heard she was a mom at one point and so I said yeah but it's like I never said anything
about them or anything and someone said something about them I said don't talk about kids but it's
like then that turned into like a thing oh he's talking about kids I mean it's like whatever I'm
talking about baby goats I said Christine uh you know Christine I saw Christine around a fire
Sacrificing babies and stuff like that baby goats and then she got to offense to it. Her name isn't even Christine
She named herself fake Christine after after the Stephen King book about a killer car
So, you know, and she's as ugly and as big as like a Dotson or whatever
Well, I'm not thoughts. I'm a Mitsubishi. I don't know
She's just a fucking ugly ugly old horror and it's like this bitch is giving me trouble and it's like really really
I mean fuck. I mean, it's like
um jeez i mean i can't even take it anymore okay i can't take it it's like it's like it's getting too
it's about to get stupid okay it is giving you trouble oh yeah kate yeah kate's running
a boycott on me kate donated a thousand dollars to zea by the way you know according to him
yeah
But what I don't know, but she but Zaya said that you know, I have the clip of that Zaya said well
Kate's talking about groomers and stuff like that Kate donated a thousand dollars to me plus thousand dollars of
Berries laundered money or whatever right and so oh and she's like I didn't do that
But you know what here's what's true that you're protecting a predator. I mean, it's like which I'm not even doing right?
It's like I mean, it's like it's so
And then it's like, and everyone's on her side.
I mean, it's like, and everyone's on Sandman's side
and Bita's side.
And these are the biggest reach hearts
in the fucking universe.
I mean, really.
It's weird cause they don't even get along with each other.
I know Kate doesn't like those people,
but like they're all against you now.
That's so weird.
Oh, she wants to be friends with Bita again.
the
to me the donkey look all horrible and disease and like dripping with like we
know I don't even know it was a horrible donkey she made I mean it's a really I
mean I don't know me that picture I think let's pack yourself up for a
barrier or something like that because I know she doesn't have the I mean her
her AI photo of herself looks like you know Christina Aguilera with like
dark hair I mean it's like I mean it's like really ridiculous how I mean it's
easy if you see her she does look like Shrek she like literally looks like a
goblin over over no no I've seen Kate she's
and I've seen a lot of ugly people in here.
Well, just say she's rough.
Okay, well, she's rough.
Yeah, that's being nice about it.
Yeah, I'm being nice.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, he's being nice.
You wanna see the picture she did of me
and how she looks in the picture instead?
Look at this shit.
Okay, I'll show you the pictures that she did of me.
So here, oh, I mean, it's a careless K.
Okay, this is what the picture she did of me.
and as it as this donkey should put up my face on this donkey or whatever right and it's like and she looks like you know
No, I saw that I I think I'm actually something that she's trying to make yourself look I
Know I know you G BG fuck yourself faggot go ahead and I like you either
I mean it's like or I don't care people don't like me go ahead go fuck yourself. You're a bitch. You're just a bitch
You're just came
Yeah, he just it was BG in the chat. He's just a bitch. He's a bit come on the panel
I don't get it like what they're bitches. They're fucking cowardly bitches. I mean, it's like really they're sad
Guys come on the panel man. Don't make don't make it boring. They're afraid. They're afraid
They're told just go in there if you're gonna talk shit to them
Don't don't go in there to like actually like participate or no jump on the panel. It's more fun. Bitch. She's not going to he's not going
She's just a bitch but watch you won't come up. No, don't be don't be gay
He has a porn bomb me because you know
RG porn bomb me
Q porn bomb me like these are the new moral voices these doxers these criminals are literal criminals doing criminal fucking
Like they're literal criminals
Like and then I was like, but what have I done? Okay. Well covering you got to cover your screen
I went to jail for three days for a possession like when I was in 2018
I went to I went to county jail, you know, because I bother to do that than we need to service
Anyway, no, there's a lot of speculation of substance abuse and things like that
No, no, there's not any steps. I'm on alcohol. My alcohol sometimes weed when I can afford it, which I
Barely ever afford it. I'm on I like, you know easy bought me some some of these cut water
He's such a bitch. He's such a bitch. I mean, it's like
No, no, no, no BG easy. He's an awesome guy
No easy awesome guy BG is a bitch
Because he's not coming on panel. He's afraid. Okay?
BG right you're afraid because you could have come up in a second, but you have to talk in the chat like a little bitch
All only bitches are in the chat like it's not ever not everyone in the chat of the bitch
But only bitches just stay in the chat and not don't don't say anything
I mean, it's like and so there's no one even banned from the panel except for RG
Clumsies ban from the brand from the panel and Q because they poor mommy or
Or just want to come up and say, oh PDF supporter or whatever like that.
I mean, they're just bitches.
I mean, it's so sick.
I mean, it's like really, I mean, it's like.
I can't even take it anymore. I mean it's like a really it's like
Can you can I believe abducted by aliens, please can aliens just come here and take me away from this earth?
Because it's like I'm not gonna do anything myself
I just want to fall in love with an alien maybe and maybe it maybe they'll they'll be like someone cool
I can't take it. You're not banned
Where are you banned and then I see you in the chat. You're not banned from the Jan
Yeah, but I'm up you're you know banned on the studio
No, no, no, there's zero people ban on my stream yard.
There's zero, I unbanned everyone in the chat.
You're not banned.
If you're banned, how do I see your comment?
If you're banned, I wouldn't see that.
Okay, so you're a liar.
You're a liar.
Okay, you're just a liar.
No, don't be gay get your asses up here. If you got something to say
Kidding just kidding. I know it's like my band. I'm yes. I'm man from like every panel
I'm you know, you know who you know who was the one person that was nice to me was Victoria J
And I went into her chat. Okay. She's joke. Okay. It's okay. It's okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Scott yeah, come on Lava get up here Lava Jan anyone come up and like talk with the you know
Everyone's like kind of scared. You don't have to be you don't have to show your face. You just have to like have your voice
I don't get it like what is I don't understand why no one wants to go on the panel
Well porn bomb me, but I mean it's like really and I don't know how I got a strike for whatever like for that
For doing nothing basically I deleted the live so someone to go back. Okay. We have jammery coming up
Okay, I'm gonna put up the thing for a minute. I want to talk to you
Jan Marie, do you know who Jan is? I think if it's the Jan I'm thinking of okay. I'm gonna put up Jan Marie
Yeah, I know Jan Marie. Okay. Well, let's have let's check her out Jan
What's up? Hi, what's up? I'm so I'm sorry. I didn't see I see JT over here rolling around in blackface. Oh
You already know fuck yeah
That's cool psyche. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Hey, I'm sorry. I know I thought you were like one of those
Cuz I'm you know Jan, right?
Yeah, she's Ziggy's ex girlfriend are you chicken? Are you chicken? Are you chicken somebody? Are you the chicken lady?
Yes, I'm the chicken lady. Okay. Okay. Yeah, Jan's chicken army, right?
Yes, okay. Okay. And I do know and I'm sorry. I ended my panel that day a little early and stuff like that
But okay, I'm glad you're here. Okay. Thank you
You're fine. You don't ever have to feel like you got to stay around for me
No, no, no, I mean because I like you and it's like I don't want to like
I don't want people to take things the wrong way because there's some people that like do look do love me
And I don't want them to think that I'm talking about them when I'm with people that hate me and the people that are
Fucking fucking with me and stuff like that and a lot of people are and so maybe I'm a little traumatized and stuff
And I don't know who to trust sometimes, but I do. I'm so happy. I have good people here. All right, Spiky
Oh, I don't want to cut you off, Jen
No, the truth is trust no one
Except for yourself
Right, but I do trust a minute because I can't like cut myself off. No, I don't just cut myself. I'm not talking about
Isolating. I'm just saying at the end of the day the only judgment that matters
Is yours that that doesn't mean that you know, you don't have your people that you trust but
Right. I just don't want people to get offended by what I'm saying, but I don't want them to think that I'm calling everybody out and stuff like that, because then people will get mad at me and stuff.
I'm a loving person. I really am a loving person. I actually came to the earth to bring love to the earth. I'm not comparing myself to Jesus, but I'm pretty much as close to Jesus as you can get nowadays.
I really am I think this is the way I love are you entering your your Christ saga like
He died at 33. I'm I did it for 55. I don't I don't know but I mean it's like but
I thought I would die at 30 years old
Like I really did and so any like all my life right now is a bonus
I'm able to help people if I'm able to if I'm not helping people if I'm not like funny if I'm not
At least making people smile sometimes
It's not going to be worth it for me.
Oh, look at the chickens.
Oh, those are beautiful chickens.
Look at it.
They are.
You know, there's a catalog.
Martha Stewart used to put this catalog.
I actually got this catalog and it has these eggs.
They look like Easter eggs.
And it's like these exotic Japanese chickens and stuff
like that.
There are some amazing chickens you can buy.
Do you know what this catalog is called?
There's a catalog where you buy chickens and stuff.
No, I mean there's a there's a couple of suppliers. I buy only like US supplier stuff
I don't try to
rare eggs, but these um, I actually have a couple of Easter eggers that lay pink and blue eggs
Like Easter they look like Easter eggs ever. Okay. What is it called? Let me see if I can find the catalog
What is called? Okay, I can't find it
But I used to get this chicken catalog and it has these beautiful eggs and there's like these exotic chickens
and you can buy the eggs of your chicken farm.
So my mom has a chicken coop.
And so she gets these fresh eggs and stuff like that.
And it's like, they really are like the best eggs,
like the best, I mean, it's really,
oh, look at that, they're your kitty cat.
Hi, yeah, this is church as church. Um, well, okay. So actually
Psyche yes, I had it. I have a question for you. Sure. So I have I have a friend
I'm putting together a care package for a friend who is coming out next month since it's pride month they
Were aiding to come out of the closet next month. What do you suggest I put in that package?
I think I have good like gay things.
Okay, so he's gonna get a gay thing.
Okay, so you know, of course a good rainbow flag
for them to put on their,
if they want to put it on their porch or something like that
or even inside their house or something like that.
A good rainbow, I don't have rainbow flags.
I'm like, you know, but I think maybe a sex toy.
I don't know.
See it's like really.
So this guy is like a real twinkie kind of guy.
Like I get the sense he probably likes unicorns
and like pink things.
Yeah.
Get him a get him a subscription international mail. There's a there's a there's a there's actually like this company
I used to when I was a teenager
I was I got the international mail catalog and it is like the gayest. I mean
I mean, it's the mother load of gay perfect
fucking perfect
I was like, tell my mom, I was like, for Christmas when I was like 16, 17, I was like, give me something for this catalog.
I think she got me a, I was like a leather bracelet or something like that.
But everything else like speedos and, you know, you know, and I do have a nice American flag speedo.
Thank you.
Easy.
Um, what else are you in the package that, you know, it's like.
Well, I found some, I found some actually some rainbow,
they've got a rainbow flag, they're condoms,
they're not rainbow colored, but they have rainbow flag
and they said, wear with pride.
And I was like, well, that's perfect.
So, you know,
if it is throw a speedo in there, I don't know
if it's American flag speedo or a rainbow flag speedo,
throw a speedo in there, piece of twink.
It's like it may be stuff for the gay parade. I don't know where he lives, but it's like it
There's usually like a gay parade in june florida. He lives in florida
Right there. Let me look at yeah, he's like a twink, but he's like bald and older
Yeah, imagine a mr. Queen if he had a real bad coat problem
Okay, mr. Queen with coat problem. Let me see florida
Gay, I mean look at florida gay pride real quick because I'm you know like lord of the rings, you know the little guy who's like
You know, he wants the ring for himself. Yeah, it's like that. It's like that. Okay. So in Fort Lauderdale, there there's numerous pride events
Miami Fort Lauderdale tell them to go to those places, you know
LGBTQ scene and it's like there's Miami Beach
Pride Fest those are good thing. I think they're probably June. I think that's when the pride is
So there is it's coming up really soon
Oh, yeah, dude, I mean like he lives in Florida and I imagine pride month June is just gonna be
Poppin or whatever the kids say
Like really, I mean, it's like and there's gay other gay guys. There's good-looking gay guys. I mean, it's like
Um, if you have any if you're any kind of good-looking
You know, you're you're all set. You're gonna have guys hitting on you and it's just it's fun
There's a bit straight people go to them, too
there's like I love a straight supporters of it and stuff like that and
It's open-minded people that just like like gay people
Someone like a you know, they're I stroke off. Yeah
Yeah, I mean he really he really needs to have some fun like he has been he's been under a lot of stress lately
Um, he's been having meltdown after meltdown after meltdown over this guy that he
Really likes on the internet
Um, that's not that's not gay and actually he's a girlfriend. Yeah, right
So he needs to cut loose and have some fun
Oh that straight guy finished you which is like really difficult finish for a gay guy to have because like
90% of the time nothing's ever gonna happen, but yeah
I mean, it's like I do I do I'm attracted to straight men and kind of or even like I'm not attracted to like the real flamboyant
Gay guys, like that's my thing. My thing is like real masculine guys
I'm kind of feminine in my own way and stuff like that
And I'm almost like the not a twinkie a twinkie anymore, but I guess I used to be I don't know
I'm just like real skinny and like, you know
I'm at the end of the day. I'm still I have a masculine side to I guess like, you know, Q
I mean heavy and I don't know if you've seen
Have you seen the key? Have you seen the Q video? Like, uh, you know with Q45, I have to show you this real quick
This is because Alexander may have made this. I don't know if you saw this
Q so Alexander made this. This is like a cult recruitment video. I guess it would be called. It's called join the cult
Okay, and this is a real this is like because I do want to meet Q at one point before he started like the boycott against me
But it's called join the cult. This is by Alexander mayors on IP to wiki.info
and uh yeah here it is just watch this real quick video and uh okay she made this for her she made
this for me or she made this for the cult because she's the high priestess here okay so here we go
um and i'll show the screen and enjoy this this is funny you'll love it
yeah
so they can see me before i even spoke i don't know about that but i'm still here
i've been walking in circles baby losing my direction same old face is selling perfect projections
everybody says i forgot the truth but i don't even know what i'm supposed to do then you show up
on my feet like a premonition cards on the table digital visions who say boy i rail with your
avoiding yeah you got a way of making silence feel loud they say you're dangerous say it's all a game
but you're the only one calling me by name you said join the group
No feeling, no crashing, just getting closer to you
come see me don't overthink it but i freeze every time i get close to the edge of it because the
world's got opinions on what this means and i don't even know what i'm feeling in yeah maybe
it's more than illusions something about you got me questioning conclusions every symbol
every line you draw feels like truth i've been running from and the voices in my head keep telling
me to run but i'm tired of
Pressure, just you're getting closer to your own sin
And the talk they'll judge, but what's that worth
When you ain't even livin' in your own world?
Join the cult, no shame, no hiding
No more running, no more dividing
Step out the script, they built body, find your truth
Join the cult
it off but my chest starts burning all this time i've been standing still while the world
keeps asking me to feel if i stay i'm safe but i'm fading if i go i might stop changing maybe
that's the risk i need to finally be something real no more asking no more waiting no more living
like i'm fading
I told you to hold, you find yourself when you join the call
That was very nice. Thank you so much. Hey, you're beautiful
Are you Jan's chicken army? You're not you know, but you're not the other lady
I mean I meant the other lady the other lady that's there's another chicken lady, right?
There's probably a bunch of chicken ladies here on the internet. Yeah, but the one that was on Jan or a Crystal-Marie show
Or Crystal Anne's show, Crystal Anne.
You're not that one.
No, no, no.
I don't go a lot of places.
Yeah, because that lady was like defending people.
I mean, she's trying to be in the cool person's group,
I guess, but then defending.
It's crazy.
It is crazy.
I don't know if you're following, but oh my god.
Um, yeah, do you know who Crystal Ann is?
Crystal Ann is?
I don't, I don't know.
I really don't know, I don't know a lot of people.
Like I know the streamers, I know like whose panel it is and stuff,
but I don't do a lot of places and I don't really talk to a whole lot of people.
Yeah, well Chris. Okay. Yeah. Well, this is that there's another chicken lady. I don't know
But yeah, it was a chicken guy like is it I want to I want to visit these chicken farm someday
I left his discord. I do leave the discord because I get like weird vibes sometimes from some people but
Well
Yeah, that that's good and good luck with that
But I left I left is the score. I left it. I'm kind of I'm kind of tired of talking about
Yeah, I know I mean that's
Two two and a half years of like
Just retired like retardation. I'm tired of it. I'm already seen his name
I'm sorry, that was my bad, my bad, my bad.
It's all right, it's all right.
I have, like someone bought me these cut waters tonight.
I don't know if you see me, I call it cold water,
but it's cut water, oh, cut waters.
I don't know where he went, but have you had these?
Longer when I see, uh-uh.
And I'm long enough to see, I had the,
what's it, I had this one, I had this one, the Mai Tai.
Oh, JT loves it.
Mai Tai, they're 12.5% alcohol.
And I had this one to drink, the Strawberry Margarita.
Oh nice, so yeah, but I just want to thank you. Thank you for coming on the show and so I mean, yeah, yeah
I mean, it's like
I like to have fun and like just like
And I'm happy there's like 26 people in here. So obviously, you know
But there's not many people talking in the chat.
I don't know if they're scared.
I'd say I just really don't know
if people are really scared, like lurkers.
There's bullies.
I mean, there's really bullies
and it's like they're scaring people.
Like that they'll like, what?
All right, what do you think?
Guys, if I can handle it, you can handle it.
Brandon can deal with it.
Here you go, Sike.
Hey, there we go.
Look at the big legs.
See the blue eggs while they're...
covered in shit right now. I'll see the blue and pink ones. These are the Easter eggers.
Yeah, those are beautiful. So is that a special chicken? Like what kind of chicken is that?
An Easter egg is usually a mix. Usually it's a hybrid. There are two chickens that lay
blue eggs. So it's usually like a
Silverlaced winded and an Americana, so they breed chickens that laid blue eggs and
So you have a special rooster
No, no, I I
Had a rooster
Okay, somebody gave me and they said it was a cinnamon queen and I was like well, that's good cuz I have
I have a cinema queen and I have some golden comments
which are all in the genealogy of Rhode Island Reds.
So that'll work, that will work.
Well, I finally got to the point
where I incubated some eggs and they hatched
and they grew up and they started laying in eggs
and one of them,
Started laying blue eggs, and I was like what the fuck so I started researching it and found out that these were the chickens
These were the kind of chickens that laid blue eggs and one of them was an Americana
And when I looked at a picture of an Americana rooster it looked
very similar to
The rooster that I had since look well, okay, he wasn't at all what I thought he was
he was this kind of rooster because he...
I'm good, sorry.
Because his jeans gave me that chicken that laid blue egg.
That's the only chicken I've got that lays blue egg.
The rest of them lay like a pinkish or a brownish color.
Now, can I show you a couple of chickens
and you can see if you can identify them?
Sure.
I wanna see your, so here's a chicken
and tell me if you recognize this chicken.
Okay, do you recognize this chicken right here?
Downloads here we go. Look at this one
Um
That a rooster is a rooster has a gullet where I don't know if it's a rooster or chicken. That is called a Poland chicken
Yeah, I was about to say that's a Polish breed the Polish breeds are the ones that have those those fucking
Crazy-ass feathers on look at this one. Look at this one. They look like Muppets. This one real. Look at that chicken
Yeah, that's a real chicken. Wow. What do you know what that's called? No
Um, let me see if I have the name of it. Okay. We're gonna go back. Um, it's probably a laced something
It looks it says it's a valley hatchery. Let me see and that's a pole
It's another Polish chicken the world through the poultry world. So Poland has these great chickens, I guess, right? Yeah
That's a me. Hey, but can you order a Polish chicken? I
Would I
you can you can order you can order a clutch of eggs and you can incubate like
fertilized eggs and you can incubate them or you can buy them from breeders but
you can't just buy one. What is that one? You can buy them from a hatchery but you
can't just buy one. Have you seen that one? You got to buy them like I mean
however they sell them but it's more than just one. Yeah the one on the screen
No
Yeah, that one is called a
That is called it's another Polish chicken now. I want to show you because you like birds, right? I
Like chickens
Okay, I want to show you
Something called the there's these are called the secret of birds of paradise. Okay
Have you heard of the birds of paradise
Check out the
Again, I think you might enjoy this. Here we go. Okay. Check this out birds of paradise
Or here right here
Look at the tail
It's pretty you're South American
Yeah, there's um, there's a plant called the bird of paradise too. We got a tail. You leave that
He's in South America. Look at the beak on that thing. Yeah, there's quite a beak
Have you ever seen or have you excuse me? Have you ever seen and heard a desert rain frog?
No, you have the sound
No, I don't have the sound but if you look it up you you can find it on YouTube
It's like a like a minute-long video of a or maybe 40 seconds of a desert rain frog
I'm gonna look that up. Yeah, I should have a pair of that. Oh look at that. Oh
Shut the fuck up get out of here
Out of here guys. Imagine being a janny. Can you get them out of the checkwise?
You guys guys mods. Can you please help me out, please?
Yeah, it's almost like a pigeon
Where's the where's the where's the one?
Is that a kingfisher
It's like a huh. Yeah, look at that tail. I mean, it's an amazing tail
Do this one look at this one?
Ooh that beak that's crazy. I love bird watching
These are gorgeous birds. I mean it's like I have I have in my office. I have a window
Then there's a tree on the far side of the window outside and I hang like bird feeders and stuff in there so I can watch the birds all day.
You like this? Yeah, I like the sounds. It's peaceful.
33 inch hat oh shit, that's like a turkey
Fisher, right? Yeah
What were you telling me about you tell me about a frog desert rain frog
Okay, I found it
Bring it right now
Wow, it's the world's cutest frog the desert rain frog guys, right? Oh my god
Oh, sorry. Sorry. There you go. That's okay
So that's here. Let's see this unit right here
Go on go on
Here we go. Here's a desert rainforest
Desert rainforest is right here
Look at this small guy guys. This is amazing. You see this
I don't know why that tickles me so much, but it damn sure does.
That's good.
There's another one, I guess.
This is the cutest noise.
This is all sandy. Oh my god, look at his eyes.
This is the Bushfalt Rainfrog and much like the other frogs in the genus Breviseps they
have a rather comical appearance with their plump round bodies, short stubby limbs and
Fasorial by nature they spend a great deal of their lives underground, only surfacing
when weather conditions are favourable, and usually with the intention to feed.
Being unable to jump, they waddle along the surface in search of food, and once they found
it, in an almost chameleon-like fashion they propel their sticky tongues and lap up insects.
This happens.
So let's slow things down a little.
The footage we're about to see was shot at 240 frames per second.
Once they've located an ant's nest they will patiently set at its entrance using their powerful sticky tongues
They'll lap up its inhabitants in a remarkable display that is characteristic of the magnificent bush felt rain frog
Yeah, Jenny's a pedophile by the way by the way guys. Oh
My god
Who is Jenny that Jenny's clip
Sandy and cute
Intense oh man, that's fucking cute
How can you be mad at that?
What is this?
Oh
Oh my god imagine it looks like Kate the turtle
Look at his mouth. Oh my god. That is a gorge.
Thank you for introducing me to that. I thank you so much.
Oh, you're welcome. I know I know Dawson kitty Dawson kitty your pedophile by the way
I'm gonna call everyone that comes in here saying that is a pedophile, right? Yeah, you are you are we know
We know you are you're trying to track from yours from your take attention from yourself call everyone else set
That's that's the oldest trick in the book pedophiles. Okay, so yeah
There you go
So I think I'm gonna end but I want to thank you for coming up when I'm gonna start again later
But I love
You're my new friend, okay? Okay. Thank you. Okay. Thank you for being brave enough at least to come up here and talk to me
You know, not a lot of people. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
Welcome I'll talk to you soon. Okay. Thank you everybody. Bye
the silence think it's empty space think a quiet life means a fragile place no
crowd around no noise no show so they assume there's nowhere else to go they
lean back start cutting corn as slow
It's just a shift you miss between the lines
Crowd just to survive